<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<app version="1">
	<name>Homebrew Browser</name>
	<coder>teknecal</coder>
	<version>0.3.9e</version>
	<release_date>201210070000</release_date>
	<short_description>Browse homebrew apps</short_description>
	<long_description>The Homebrew Browser allows you to download the latest homebrew applications and games all through your Wii. You don't need to take your SD card out. You don't even need a computer! You can also delete homebrew you no longer want.

No more dead links, no more extracting files, no more finding out that the homebrew application doesn't include an icon.png and meta.xml in the zip file! 

Icons:
Green Tick - You have the latest version of that homebrew application installed.
Yellow Question Mark - You might not have the latest version of that homebrew application installed.

Controls:
A Button = Click Button
B Button = Cancel Download or Extracting
Hold B button - Move the Wiimote up and down to scroll through the list quickly
D Pad Left/Right = Change category
D Pad Up/Down = Scroll up and down the list slowly
Minus/Plus Button = Delete/Remove/Add application to download/delete queue
Home Button = Menu
Hold Home Button down = Return to loader
1 Button = Work offline
2 Button = Revert to CodeMii repository

Author:
teknecal (teknecal@gmail.com) - www.codemii.com
Graphics by DayDreamOz (www.spriteattack.com)

History:
7 October 2012 (v0.3.9e)
- Updated with latest libogc which should correct network issues some users are experiencing

17 September 2012 (v0.3.9d)
- Added support for new Wiimote 
- Added a longer timeout when requesting the homebrew list

25 February 2011 (v0.3.9c)
- Fixed connecting to the backup server
- Added setting to allow use of secondary server whenever you like

31 October 2010 (v0.3.9b)
- Added secondary CodeMii server
- Added a connection test so HBB doesn't look frozen if it can't connect to the server

21 October 2010 (v0.3.9a)
- Really fixed bug with HBB calculating the wrong free space
- Fixed bug when trying to use other repositories apart from CodeMii
- Added setting to enable/disable HBB from checking for updates


Credits:
LowLines for the Homebrew Browser v0.2.x graphics including logo, HBC icon and all other graphics
joedj - ftpii source for network read and write
NoNameNo &amp; Redshare - GRRLIB (3.0)
Tantric - Unzip library
All the Wii homebrew developers and icon artists
All the people who tested the HBB revisions
Team Twiizers, #wiidev &amp; #wiihelp

Misc:
Want to be notified when applications are updated?
Add hbb@codemii.com to your Wii address book
For more information about HBB and developments visit: www.codemii.com

Visit the homebrew developers on IRC at irc.efnet.org at #wiidev
Need help with running homebrew on your Wii? Visit #wiihelp</long_description>
</app>